NAMITA KANDWAL DUA

Email:

kandwalnamita1997@gm ail.com

Contact No.

Mobile: +91 8860743692

Permanent Address

New Colony Palwal, Haryana

District:

Palwal

State:

Haryana

Country:

India

Pin code: 121102

Date of Birth

12th Aug, 1997

Marital Status

Married

Linguistic Proficiency

English, Hindi

Strengths-

Multitasking, Talent Acquisition, Team Management, Report Preparation, Employee Engagement, Data Handling

OBJECTIVE

Goal-oriented Human Resources specialist with 3.6 years of successful experience in Talent Acquisition, Operations and Administration. Worked with industries like E-commerce, Edu. Tech and IT, looking forward for a managerial position or Individual Contributor in a reputable organization to utilize her ability and skills in ensuring an effective HR Unit.

WORK EXPERIENCE

StartBlocks Pvt Ltd.

Designation: - HR- Assistant Manager (22nd June 2022- Present)

Key Responsibilities-

- Managing the Talent Acquisition part (Hiring for Admission Officer, Visa officer, Admission Councilor, Business Analyst, Team Manager, graphic designer and others non-Tech)
- Taking On boarding, induction, salary discussion and Managing Employees Master Data, Attendance Management, Freelancer payout and other operational works.
- Creating letters like offer letter, Appointment letter, Policies for the company and other official documents.
- Handing the Separation department (exit interview, FNF, Letters)

DataTrained Education Pvt. Ltd.

Designation: - HR- Assistant Manager (7th June 2021- 15th June 2022)

Key Responsibilities-

- Handling team of 5 members.
- Giving training and helping the team with internal recruitment.
- Coordinating with the External recruitment team for hiring, billing, and replacement.
- Maintain the Payroll of the employees, freelancer invoice, and Intern.
- Handling the Full Recruitment, Admin, and Operation department of the organization.
- Recruit IT and Non-IT staff (Sales bulk Hiring, Graphic designer, Accountant, Placement Officer, Trainers, Data Scientist, AVP and managers)
- Handling the Separation process of the employees (Conducting exit interviews, exit documentation, FNF, creating relieving documents)
- On boarding the new joiners, giving orientation, joining documentation.
- Conducting interviews of students for the placement services.
- Implementation of PF and ESIC, coordinating with compliance team for the payment, coordinating with finance team for Tax related documentation.

DataTrained Education

Designation: - HR- Assistant Manager (1st Sep 2020 -6th June 2021)

Key Responsibilities-

- Handling team of 5 members.
- Responsible for the internal recruitment of Tech and Non-tech.
- Coordinating with the External recruitment team for hiring, billing, and replacement.
- Maintain the Payroll of the employees.
- Handling the Admin and Operation department of the organization.

- Handling the Separation process of the employees (Conducting exit interviews, exit documentation, FNF, creating relieving documents)
- Implemented HRMS like Kredily and HROne in the organization and even worked on datatrained internal portals.
- Conducting interviews of students for the placement services.

DataTrained Education

Designation: - HR Cum Career Coach (June 2020- 1st Sep 2020)

Key Responsibilities-

- Handling Talent Acquisition department (Taking Interviews, Salary negotiation, and Employee Onboarding)
- Creating employment letters (offer letter and Appointment Letter).
- Maintain Employees documents in electronic and paper form.
- Solving quarries of employees and the students enrolled in the programs offer by the organization.
- Maintaining Payroll structure of employees, variable (monthly, quarterly and yearly), and incentives if any.

iDreamBiz

Designation: - HR Generalist (Nov 2019- May 2020) Key Responsibilities:

- Handling talent acquisition and recruitment process (internal + external).
- Conduct employee on boarding
- Provide support to employees in various HR-related topics such as leaves, compensation and resolve any issues that may arise.
- Maintaining employees' files and records in electronic and paper form.
- Enhance job satisfaction by resolving issues promptly, applying new perks and benefits and organizing team building activities.
- Highly positive attitude, adaptable to demanding situations.

DIGITONE MOBILES Pvt. Ltd

<u>Designation: Operations Specialist (Oct 2018 – Oct 2019) Key Responsibilities:</u>

- Handle online portals of achhamall, Meesho and Flipkart (Listing products).
- Analyzing and interpreting the Data.
- Managing the warehouse and processing the payments.
- Engaged with the Social Marketing team- facebook, intagram, Pintrest and connecting with the Youtubers for the promotions.
- Managing Online Campaign.
- Handling customers and client quarries via telephonic, mail, chat support.
- Analyzing and maintaining the data of slow- and fast-moving products.
- Coordinating with the delivery agents for the on-time delivery.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- □ B.Com (Bachelor of Commerce) from SOL Delhi University, June 2018).
- □ 12th from Army Public School, Mhow (CBSE Board), March 2015.
- □ 10th from Army Public School, Mhow (CBSE Board), March 2013.

	Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint Operating system: Windows, Ubuntu.
DECLARATION	
l hereb	y declare that the information given above is true & correct to the best of my knowledge.
Date:	

[Namita Kandwal Dua]

COMPUTER PROFICIENCY

Place: